Guide to the Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
Music Department Records: Series 3, Concert Programs, 1863-[ongoing]
- Series 3. Concert Programs, 1878-[ongoing]
  - General Concerts
    - September 30, 1988: Anthony and Joseph Paratore: Duo-Pianists, performed by Anthony Paratore, Joseph Paratore (Box 5)
    - October 8, 1988: Experimental Music, performed by Ron Kuivila, Alvin Lucier, Terry Riley (Box 5)
    - October 8-9, 1988: Wesrevue VII, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - October 12, 1988: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 5)
    - October 14, 1988: The Jazz Connection, performed by The New World Consort, Roy Wiseman (Box 5)
    - October 15, 1988: Traditional and Contemporary Music for Koto and Shakuhachi, performed by Reiko Kamata, Ralph Samuelson (Box 5)
    - October 21-22, 1988: The Wesleyan Concert Choir and Orchestra, performed by The Wesleyan Concert Choir, Robert Ford, The Wesleyan Orchestra, Melvin Strauss (Box 5)
    - November 4, 1988: George Russel and the Living Time Orchestra, performed by George Russell, Dizzy Gillespie (Box 5)
    - November 12, 1988: Jazz, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe, Fred Simmons, Ed Blackwell, Wes Brown, Ted Curson, The Wesleyan University Big Band (Box 5)
    - November 18, 1988: From Josquin to Lasso: The Netherlandish Vocal Art, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Robert Ford (Box 5)
    - December 2, 1988: The Bowdoin Trio, performed by Jon Klibonoff, Alexander Simionescu, Semyon Fridman (Box 5)
    - December 3, 1988: The Wesleyan University Orchestra with the Bowdoin Trio, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Alan Gosman, Bowdoin Trio (Box 5)
    - December 9, 1988: West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzinyah, Freeman K. Donkor, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 11, 1988: Gloria in Excelsis: The 60th Annual Candlelight Concert at Wesleyan University, performed by TheConcert Choir, The Wesleyan Singers, The Wesleyan Orchestra, Direct by Robert Ford (Box 5)
    - December 14, 1988: Ronald Ebrecht: Organist, performed by Ronald Ebrecht (Box 5)
    - January 20, 1989: Opera Scenes, performed by Phyllis Bruce, Wayne Rivera, George Creeger, Neely Bruce, Peter Standaart (Box 5)
    - January 25, 1989: Charles Krigbaum: Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 5)
    - January 27, 1989: Los Angeles Guitar Quartet, performed by Anisa Angarola, John Dearman, William Kanengiser, Scott Tennant (Box 5)
    - February 11, 1989: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Weleyan University Big Band, Bill Barron (Box 5)
    - February 18, 1989: Afro-American Music, performed by Bill Barron, Bill Lowe, Ed Blackwell, Fred Simmons, Wes Brown (Box 5)
    - February 19, 1989: Clark-Schuldmann Duo, performed by Harry Clark, Sandra Schuldmann (Box 5)
    - February 24, 1989: Due, Tre, Avanti! (((1)+1)+1): Combinations of Three Musicians, performed by Mary Ann Liniak-Bodwell, Naomi Amos, Peter Standaart (Box 5)
    - Febraury 25, 1989: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan Uniersity Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Alan Gosman (Box 5)
    - March 3, 1989: New York Cornet & Sacbut Ensemble, performed by Allan Dean, Ben Peck, Ronald Borror, Terry Pierce, David Titcomb, Peter Becker (Box 5)
    - March 4 and 15, 1989: Early Music Weekend, performed by The New York Cornet and Sacbut Ensemble, Peter Becker, The Wesleyan Choruses, Robert Ford, The Wesleyan Singers, et al. (Box 5)
    - March 7, 1989: Traditional Japanese Music, performed by The Students' Japanese Music Union of Kansai (Box 5)
    - March 8, 1989: Piano Duo, performed by Peter Dengenhardt, Fuat Kent, Oliver Kent (Box 5)
    - March 29, 1989: Sarah Meneely-Kyder & Company, performed by Sarah Meneely Kyder, Company (Box 5)
    - April 15, 1989: Wesleyan Universirty Big Band, performed by Wesleyan Universirty Big Band, Bill Barron (Box 5)
    - April 25, 1989: Blood Drum Spirit, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - April 28, 1989: Music by Ralph Vaughan Williams and Benjamin Britten, performed by The Wesleyan Singers, Concert Choir, Robert Ford, Ronald Ebrecht, Susan Burkhart (Box 5)
    - April 30, 1989: Wesleyan Students' Recital, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - May 3, 1989: Tibet: Sacred Music, Sacred Dance, performed by Gungbar Rinpoche, Lhating Rinpoche, Ghen Namgyal, Umzey Kunkyen, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 5, 1989: Wayang Kulit, performed by Sumarsam, I. M. Harjito, Wesleyan Gamelan Ensemble, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 6, 1989: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Melvin Strauss, Alan Gosman (Box 5)
    - Undated: Workers of the World, performed by AM/TG, Wesleyan Singers, Marni Nixon, et al. (Box 5)
    - Septmeber 22, 1989: Brass Ring, performed by Daniel D'Addio, Claire Newbold, Kristen Bendixen, David Kayser, Karl Kramer (Box 5)
    - October 7, 1989: Experimental Music, performed by Takaheisa Kosugi, Alvin Lucier, Ron Kuivila, John Zorn (Box 5)
    - October 13, 1989: World Music by American Composers, performed by New World Consort, Roy Wiseman, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 14, 1989: Susan Burkhart, Guitar, performed by Susan Burkhart, Ken Gehret (Box 5)
    - October 25, 1989: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 5)
    - October 27, 1989: Music from Korea, performed by Keith Howard, Inok Paek (Box 5)
    - November 3, 1989: Balcom & Morris, performed by Joan Morris, Wiliam Bolcom (Box 5)
    - November 4, 1989: Stravinsky + Bartok, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Wesleyan Concert Choir, Neely Bruce (Box 5)
    - November 10, 1989: Lute Vocal Recital by Carver Blanchard, performed by Carver Blanchard, et al. (Box 5)
    - November 15, 1989: Larry D. Schipull, Organist, performed by Larry D. Schipull (Box 5)
    - November 16-18, 1989: Chants of Saints and Strings 'n Things: A Three-Day Festival of Afro-American Music, performed by Keith Copland, John Stubblefield, et al. (Box 5)
    - November 21, 1989: An Evening of Japanese Music, performed by Michiyo Yagi, Yuichiro Kinoshita, Raplh Samuelson (Box 5)
    - December 2, 1989: Amida, performed by Peter Hoogenboom, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 3, 1989: Candlelight Concert, performed by Concert Choir, Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Ronald Ebrecht (Box 5)
    - December 8, 1989: George Shirley, Tenor, performed by George Shirley, Neely Bruce (Box 5)
    - December 9, 1989: Claude Debussy (1862-1918), performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 15, 1989: West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzenyah, Sara Thompson, special guest artists (Box 5)
    - January 26, 1990: Music by Benjamin Britten, performed by Sharon Dennison Perry, Julie Charland Ribchinsky, William Braun, Sandra Wehner (Box 5)
    - February 1, 1990: Charles Krigbaum: Organist, performed by Charles Krigbaum (Box 5)
    - February 4, 1990: Arditti String Quartet, performed by Arditti String Quartet (Box 5)
    - February 7, 1990: Fidelio, performed by Lois Martin, Harry Clark, Sandra Schuldmann (Box 5)
    - February 9, 1990: The Muir String Quartet, performed by Peter Zazofsky, Bayla Keyes, Steven Ansell, Michael Reynolds (Box 5)
    - February 10, 1990: In the Spirit of Bill Barron, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - February 21-24, 1990: After the Empire, performed by Andres Jimenez, Taller Campesino, The American Music/Theatre Group, Neely Bruce, Melvin Strauss, Jim Desmond, et al. (Box 5)
    - March 1, 1990: David Christiansen: Organist, performed by David Christiansen (Box 5)
    - March 2, 1990: Shakuhachi Solo Concert, performed by Yuichiro Kinoshita (Box 5)
    - March 3, 1990: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Alan Gosman, Brian Gottesman, et al. (Box 5)
    - March 27, 1990: New Traditional Music and Dance, performed by Lauren Cowdery, Cheryl Cutler, Jim Cowdery, Jim Martin, David Nelson, Sally Renti, Peter Standaart (Box 5)
    - March 28, 1990: Fidelio, performed by Lois Martin, Harry Clark, Sandra Schuldmann (Box 5)
    - April 6, 1990: Ronald Ebrecht: Organist, performed by Ronald Ebrecht (Box 5)
    - April 17, 1990: Concert of Japanese Music, performed by Yuichiro Kinoshitam, Michiyo Yagi (Box 5)
    - April 20, 1990: A Musical Tribute to Joseph Daltry, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Ronald Ebrecht (Box 5)
    - April 21, 1990: Wesleyan University Big Band, performed by Wesleyan University Big Band, John Stubblefield (Box 5)
    - April 27, 1990: 10 Pieces from 13,000 Islands: A Concert of Original Works in the Cross-Cultural Music by Ben M. Pasaribu, performed by Ben M. Pasaribu, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 28, 1990: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan Universirty Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Alan Gosman, Jasmine Sadrieh, Mark Newhouse, Abby Smith, Patricia McKenna (Box 5)
    - April 29, 1990: Japanese Music Concert - Koto + Shakuhachi, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - May 4, 1990: The Concert Choir, performed by Wesleyan Concert Choir, Neely Bruce (Box 5)
    - May 5, 1990: An Evening of Javanese Dance and Music, performed by Wesleyan's renowned gamelan ensemble, Sumarsam, I. M. Harjito, Urip Sri Maeny, guest artists (Box 5)
    - May 6, 1990: Act Four: Concert of Music by Four Composers: Wesleyan Graduate Students, performed by Ben Pasaribu, Miriam Gerberg, Landon Rose, Warren Furman, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 8, 1990: Blood Drum Spirit, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - September 13-15, 1990: Navaratri 1988: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by M. Nageswara Rao, Vijayasree Mokkapati, Ramnad Raghavan (Box 5)
    - September 21, 1990: Christopher O'Riley: Piano, performed by Christopher O'Riley (Box 5)
    - October 3, 1990: Fidelio, performed by Lois Martin, Harry Clark, Sandra Schuldmann, Brian Johnson (Box 5)
    - October 5, 1990: EurAsian Ensemble with Ihsan Ozgen, performed by Ihsan Ozgen, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 6, 1990: Brazilian Music & Jazz, performed by Julie Searles, Matthew Allen (Box 5)
    - October 12, 1990: David Starobin: Guitar, performed by David Starobin (Box 5)
    - October 13, 1990: A Tribute to the Ricciotti Ensemble, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Neely Bruce, Anthony Braxton (Box 5)
    - October 20, 1990: A concert in celebration of 20 years of coeduaction at Weleyan, performed by Cardinal Singers, Wesleyan Spirits, Cheryl L. Spencer, Wesleyan World Ensemble, et al. (Box 5)
    - November 2, 1990: The Lousiana Repertory Jazz Ensemble, performed by The Lousiana Repertory Jazz Ensemble (Box 5)
    - November 3, 1990: Guitar Recital, performed by Sue Burkhart, Ken Gehret, Tony Dominic (Box 5)
    - November 8, 1990: Recital for the Centennial of the death of Cesar Franck: November 8, 1890, performed by Craig Campbell (Box 5)
    - November 9, 1990: Experimental Music, performed by Christian Marclay, Ron Kuivila, Anthony Braxton (Box 5)
    - November 10, 1990: Drum Stories: A Concert by Ehran Yehuda Elisha, performed by Ehran Yehuda Elisha, Miki Maruta, et al. (Box 5)
    - November 16, 1990: Kenny Barron, Piano; with Ray Drummond, Bass, performed by Kenny Barron, Ray Drummond (Box 5)
    - November 30, 1990: Doriot Anthony Dwyer: Flute, performed by Doriot Anthony Dwyer, Deborah Emery (Box 5)
    - December 2-3, 1990: Wesleyan University Ebony Singers Winter Concert, performed by Ebony Singers, Cynthia Nelson, Timothy Crump (Box 5)
    - December 4, 1990: Koto and Shakuhachi Student Recital, performed by Koto students, Miki Maruta, Shakuhachi students, Tomie Hahn (Box 5)
    - December 8-9, 1990: The Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Neely Bruce, the Concert Choir, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 12, 1990: Psalms and Owls and Southern Songs, and some other stuff not appropriate to the season, performed by Wesleyan Singers, Neely Bruce, Ronald Ebrecht, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 13, 1990: The Groove, the Whole Groove, and Nothing but the Groove, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - December 14, 1990: West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Students of Abraham Adzenyah, Sarah Kwarkua Thompson (Box 5)
    - December 15, 1990: Wesleyan University Large and Small Ensemble, performed by Ed Blackwell, Jay Hoggard, et al. (Box 5)
    - January 25, 1990: A Cole Porter Celebration, performed by New World Consort, Roy Wiseman, Richard Lalli, Gary Chapman (Box 5)
    - February 1, 1991: Laurentian String Quartet; Cassatt String Quartet, performed by Laurentian String Quartet, Cassatt String Quartet (Box 5)
    - February 2, 1991: David Hurd, Organist, performed by David Hurd (Box 5)
    - February 8, 1991: New Music Mini-Series: Lois V. Vierk, performed by Lois V. Vierk, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 9, 1991: New Music Mini-Series: Barbara Held and Brenda Hutchinson, performed by Barbara Held, Brenda Hutchinson, et al. (Box 5)
    - Febraury 16, 1991: A Tribute to Ed Blackwell, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - February 22, 1991: Works of Neely Bruce and other Southern composers, performed by Neely Bruce, Phyllis Bruce (Box 5)
    - February 23-24, 1991: Young Organ Virtuosi at Wesleyan, performed by Andrew Risinger, Beth Melcher, Elisabeth Garner (Box 5)
    - March 1, 1991: Seymour Lipkin, Piano, performed by Seymour Lipkin (Box 5)
    - March 2, 1991: Wesleyan University Orchestra & Wesleyan Concert Choir with Guest Soloist Seymour Lipkin, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Wesleyan Concert Choir, Melvin Strauss, Seymour Lipkin, et al. (Box 5)
    - March 27, 1991: Lakshmi (Daughter of Balasaraswati): An Evening of South Indian Dance, performed by Lakshmi, T. Viswanathan, Harish Nilakantan, Matthew Allen, Douglas Knight, Jr. (Box 5)
    - April 3, 1991: Last Supper at Uncle Tom's Cabin, performed by Bill T. Jones, The Julius Hemphill Sextet, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 5, 1991: Music of Charles Eisengart: A Senior Recital, performed by Charles Eisengart, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 6, 1991: True But Irrelevant: A Senior Thesis Piano Concert by Charles Neuman, performed by Charles Neuman (Box 5)
    - April 8, 1991: Voices Performing: 20th Century American Choral Music, and Works for Smaller Ensembles, performed by Jim Desmond, Sarah Meneely-Kyder, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 9, 1991: Vakarone: An Evening of Lithuanian Music, Dance, and Food, performed by Julija Gelazis, et al. (Box 5)
    - Undated: Imitating Art: Four Compositions by Jeremy Chatzky, performed by Jeremy Chatzky, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 17, 1991: Ronald Ebrecht: University Organist, performed by Ronald Ebrecht, Stephan Tieszen, Patricia Smith-Romanski (Box 5)
    - April 19, 1991: Donald Berman, Piano, performed by Donald Berman (Box 5)
    - April 20, 1991: Wesleyan Quartet, Octet & Large Ensemble, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - April 23, 1991: A Graduate Concert by Ehran Yehuda Elisha, performed by Ehran Yehuda Elisha, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 24, 1991: Landon Rose: Graduate Concert, performed by Landon Rose, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 26, 1991: Vespers for Ss. Cletus and Marcellinus in Eastertide, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - April 27, 1991: Wesleyan University Orchestra, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Morgan Hott (Box 5)
    - April 29, 1991: Ebony Singers: Spring Concert and Live Recording Session, performed by Ebony Singers, Marichal B. Monts (Box 5)
    - May 4, 1991: Wayang Kulit, performed by Kyai Mentul, Kyai Pradah, Sumarsam, I. M. Harkito, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 5, 1991: A Program of Music Composed by Franz Schubert in 1828, the Final Year of His Life, performed by Wesleyan Concert Choir, Wesleyan Singers, soloists, Melvin Strauss (Box 5)
    - May 7, 1991: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 5)
    - May 8, 1991: Blood Drum Spirit, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - May 10, 1991: Welcome to an evening of Hindustani Classical Music and East Indian Folk Songs, performed by Ustad Kadar Khan, Stan Scott (Box 5)
    - May 11, 1991: Mozart Mania, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - May 12, 1991: Four by Four, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - May 15, 1991: An Evening of Non-Indigenous Viola Music, performed by Eva Kiss (Box 5)
    - September 11-13, 1991: Navaratri 1991: A Concert of South Indian Music, performed by T. Viswansthan, Ananthankrishnan, Ramnad Raghavan (Box 5)
    - September 20, 1991: Russell Sherman, Piano, performed by Russell Sherman (Box 5)
    - September 27, 1991: Ronald Ebrecht, University Organist, performed by Ronald Ebrecht (Box 5)
    - September 28, 1991: Cantinho do Brasil, performed by Julie Searles, Matthew Allen (Box 5)
    - October 4, 1991: Turn-stiles, performed by Carver Blanchard, Sue Blanchard, William Braun, Peter Standaart (Box 5)
    - October 5, 1991: Kazue Sawai with Sawai Koto Ensemble, performed by (Box 5)
    - October 12, 1991: Anthony Braxton Quartet, performed by Anthony Braxton, Marilyn Crispell, Gerry Hemingway, Mark Dresser (Box 5)
    - October 25, 1991: Joel Krosnick, Violoncello; Gilbert Kalish, Piano, performed by Joel Krosnick, Gilbert Kalish (Box 5)
    - November 2, 1991: Music for Merce, performed by Takehisa Kosugi (Box 5)
    - November 6, 1991: Music for Voice and Piano, performed by Paulina Stark, Sanda Schuldmann (Box 5)
    - November 9, 1991: A Program of Music by J. S. bach and his admirers, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Concert Choir, Melvin Strauss, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 1, 1991: Alvin Lucier: Concert of Solo Works, performed by Alvin Lucier (Box 5)
    - December 5, 1991: A Concert of Javanese Music and Dance, performed by The Wesleyan Gamelan, I. M. Harjito, Sri Hadeni Harkito (Box 5)
    - December 6, 1991: Anne Koscielny, Piano, performed by Anne Koscielny (Box 5)
    - December 7-8, 1991: The Sixty-Third Annual Candlelight Concert, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Rob Mangels, Eva Kiss, Sriram Parasuram (Box 5)
    - December 13, 1991: West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adenyah, Sarah Thompson, guest artists (Box 5)
    - January 24, 1992: By Rodgers and Hart, performed by The New World, Richard Lalli, Gary Chapman, Roy Wiseman (Box 5)
    - January 31, 1992: New Music for Twelve Voices, performed by Neely Bruce, The American Music/Theatre Group, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 5, 1992: An Evening of Music for Two Pianos, performed by Sarah Meneely Kyder, Varonica Tomanek (Box 5)
    - February 7, 1992: Cavani String Quartet, performed by Annie Fullard, Susan Waterbury, Erika Eckert, Merry Peckham (Box 5)
    - February 14, 1992: Carnival at Wesleyan, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - February 28, 1992: I Am An American: Kurt Weill on Broadway, performed by Angelina Reaux, Robert Kapilow (Box 5)
    - February 29, 1992: A Program of Music by Kurt Weill, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, Angelina Reaux (Box 5)
    - March 27, 1992: Korby Myrick, performed by Korby Myrick, William Braun, Julia Charland Ribchinsky, Peter Standaart (Box 5)
    - April 10, 1992: Paul Orgel, Piano, performed by Paul Orgel (Box 5)
    - April 24-25, 1992: African-American Music Program Weekend, performed by Jazz Orchestra, Jay Hoggard, Small Ensemble, Ed Blackwell (Box 5)
    - April 26, 1992: The Wesleyan University Orchestra together with The Connecticut College Orchestra, performed by The Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, The Connecticut College Orchestra, Peter Sacco, Yuki Shimada (Box 5)
    - May 1, 1992: A Program of Music by Johannes Brahms, performed by Wesleyan Concert Choir, Melvin Strauss, Wesleyan Singers, Jon Barlow, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 2, 1992: A Vision and a Verisilmilitude, performed by Heather Ellsworth, et al. (Box 5)
    - May 5, 1992: Philip Prince, Organist, performed by Philip Prince (Box 5)
    - May 8, 1992: An Evening of Javanese Music and Dance, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - May 12, 1992: Blood Drum Spirit, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - September 16, 1992: Navaratri 1992: A Concert of South Indian Classical Music, performed by T. Viswanathan, A. Ananthakrishnan, Ramnad V. Raghavan, Harish Neelakandan (Box 5)
    - October 2, 1992: Aki Takahashi: Hyper Beatles, performed by Ari Takahashi (Box 5)
    - October 3, 1992: Lecture/Demonstration: History and Aesthetic of Traditional Japanese Dance and Music, performed by Kawamoto Toshie, Ishigure Masayo, et al. (Box 5)
    - October 16, 1992: William Braun: Piano, performed by William Braun, Karen Lerner, Mark Ryan, Patrick Smith (Box 5)
    - October 23, 1992: A Program of Music by Ludwig van Beethoven, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Concert Choir, Melvin Strauss, Renee Jolles, Harry Clark, Sanda Schuldmann (Box 5)
    - November 6, 1992: Ragtime Relatives: New World Consort, performed by New World Consort, Roy Wiseman (Box 5)
    - Undated: Pan is Beautiful, performed by Steel Panacea, Pandemonium, Hartford Steel Symphony, Melvin Strauss, Elizabeth Calleo, Jay Hoggard (Box 5)
    - November 13, 1992: Visiting Teachers' Concert, performed by Sarah Meneely-Kyder, Sue Burkhart, Aaron Jay Kernis (Box 5)
    - November 14, 1992: Anthony Braxton: Solo Wesleyan '92, performed by Anthony Braxton, Marilyn Crispell, Gerry Hemingway, Mark Dresser (Box 5)
    - November 19, 1992: Arditti String Quartet, performed by Irvine Arditti, David Alberman, Garth Knox, Rohan se Saram (Box 5)
    - December 5-6, 1992: The Sixty-Fourth Annual Candlelight Concert, performed by The Wesleyan Chamber Choir, Jessica Sternfield, Wesleyan Concert Choir, Wesleyan Orchestra, Melvin Strauss (Box 5)
    - December 10, 1992: An Evening of Javanese Dance and Wayang, performed by The Wesleyan Gamelan Ensemble, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 11, 1992: West African Drumming and Dance, performed by Abraham K. Adzenyah, Sara Thompson, Aziz Botchway, et al. (Box 5)
    - December 15, 1992: Vocal Music of Neely Bruce, performed by Charles Van Tassel (Box 5)
    - February 12-14, 1993: Experimental Music Mini-Festival, performed by Various (Box 5)
    - February 19, 1993: Welcome to an Evening of Vocal Music of North India, performed by Stan Scott, Soumitra Banerjee, Mohan Beltangady, Pritha Basu, Mahua Mukherjee (Box 5)
    - February 20, 1993: ecSTATistICs, performed by Markus Trunk, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 21, 1993: 1993 Rug Concert Series, performed by Lakshmi, T. Viswanathan, et al. (Box 5)
    - February 23, 1993: Brazilian Jazz: A Concert for Kayla, performed by Matthew Allen, Julie Searles, friends (Box 5)
    - February 26, 1993: James Buswell, Violin; Mark Levinson, Piano, performed by James Buswell, MarkLevinson (Box 5)
    - February 27, 1993: Music of the 1890s, performed by Wesleyan University Orchestra, Melvin Strauss, James Buswell (Box 5)
    - March 26, 1993: New Music from Ghana, performed by Abraham Adzenyah, et al. (Box 5)
    - March 30, 1993: Anthony Braxton, performed by Michael Attias, Roland Dahinden, Hildegard Kleeb, Robert Rumbolz (Box 5)
    - Undated: Ensemble Music (Wesleyan) 1993, performed by Anthony Braxton, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 2, 1993: The Massachusettes Chamber Players, performed by Jennifer Langham, Estela Kersenbaum, Olevsky, Charles Treger (Box 5)
    - April 3, 1993: The Economic Survival Rite of Passage, performed by Andruid Kerne, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 4, 1993: Inside Out: A Senior Music Project by Ben Graves, performed by Ben Graves, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 7, 1993: An Evening of Music for Two Pianos, performed by Sarah Meneely Kyder, Varonica Tomanek (Box 5)
    - April 10, 1993: Words Used: A Senior Music Project Concert by Kimberly Williams, performed by Kimberly Williams, et al. (Box 5)
    - April 10, 1993: Circular Space, performed by Jonathan Foster, Rick Meyerson, Dan Schaffer, Jonathan Trombly, Rene Musiln, Kerim Yasar (Box 5)
    - April 15, 1993: Neely Bruce: W.T.C. I on Organ (Six Fugues), performed by Neely Bruce (Box 5)